

# SHERLYNN GAIL MANICAT PARRENO

Senior Web Developer ♥ SINGAPORE, SINGAPORE | +65 8717 8689

#### O DETAILS O

Singapore, Singapore +65 8717 8689 <a href="mailto:sherlynngailparreno@gmail.com">sherlynngailparreno@gmail.com</a>

#### o LINKS o

Sherlynn Site

LinkedIn

GitHub

#### o SKILLS o

HTML5, XHTML, CSS3, JavaScript,

Custom Web Design

Web Standards, Cross-browser-Compatibility and Performance

Frontend Frameworks (Zurb, Bootstrap)

PHP Framework (Laravel)

CSS Framework (Tailwind)

End-to-End Testing (Cypress)

VueJS

Google Analytics

Search Engine Optimisation

Project Management Methodology

#### PROFILE

A highly motivated individual and excellent team player with good planning and project management. With a strong technical skill-set, attention to detail, and 8+ years solid experience in Web Development. Focused on UI development for large scale CMS websites.

#### **EMPLOYMENT HISTORY**

### Senior Web Developer at Bemyguest Pte. Ltd., Singapore

November 2015 - Present

Frontend developer responsible for the following: developing and maintaining BeMyGuest's website as well as clients' website, focusing on User interaction compatible to all devices and browsers, providing frontend system development, testing, and deployment, providing frontend lifecycle ownership from production to development and beyond.

As a frontend developer, I demonstrate fluency on web technologies including but not limited to CSS, HTML5, and Javascript. Complementing our backend team with my skills resulting to delivery of advance features. I'm also working with our engineer manager to ensure continuous system improvement in alignment with our overall vision and strategy, our sales and account development team, and all other teams including my

team to ensure that projects are delivered with quality and on time.

#### Senior Web Designer at Webnatics Pte. Ltd., Singapore

August 2011 — November 2015

Designed and developed responsive website internally and client-side, focused on user interaction across all devices and browser compatibility. Work tightly with sales and account development team in pushing projects to completion.

## Operation Quality Associate at Interactive Business Network Solution, Manila, Philippines

November 2010 — June 2011

Managed a small team who is responsible in monitoring company and competitor website. Provides training for the new employee. Also responsible in generating report and some documentation as needed. Work tightly with the Team Lead and Local Head.

#### Quality Control Associate at Stream Global Service, Makati, Philippines

July 2009 — June 2010

Verified each sales of the agent to make sure it follows the standard/protocol set. Gathers data and generate reports based on clients needs. Work tightly with Team Lead, QA HEAD and clients.

#### EDUCATION

Bachelor of Science in Information Technology, FEU-East Asia College, Manila, Philippines

June 2005 — April 2009

## COURSES

Basic Conversational Mandarin, Stanford
April 2017 — June 2017

# REFERENCES

References available upon request

## **U** CERTIFICATION

Google Analytics Individual Qualification February 2020 — February 2021